Harry Norman Gardiner papers, 1855 - 1927 (bulk 1870 - 1930)
Smith College Archives
- SERIES VI. PUBLICATIONS
  - Chapter V, manuscript undated (Box 824.1, Folder 8)
  - Chapter VI, manuscript undated (Box 824.1, Folder 9)
  - Chapter VII, manuscript undated (Box 824.1, Folder 10)
  - Chapter VIII, manuscript undated (Box 824.1, Folder 11)
  - Chapter IX, manuscript undated (Box 824.1, Folder 12)
- SERIES VII. SPEECHES
  - miscellaneous 1893, undated (Box 824.2, Folder 1)
  - Aristotle Club 1895 (Box 824.2, Folder 2)
  - Chapel 1894 - 1926 (Box 824.2, Folder 3)
  - "Civic Betterment", Christmas Cove 1925 (Box 824.2, Folder 4)
  - "Ectoplasm and the Physical Phenomena of Spiritualism" undated (Box 824.2, Folder 5)
  - "Ethics and Evolution", Connecticut Valley Congregational Club 1897 (Box 824.2, Folder 6)
  - "Feeling and Will" undated (Box 824.2, Folder 7)
  - Gardiner House Dinner 1926 (Box 824.2, Folder 8)
  - "Green's Testament of the Relation of Feeling to Reality" undated (Box 824.2, Folder 9)
  - "The Heritage of the Pilgrims in the Church", Smith College Tercentenary 1920 (Box 824.2, Folder 10)
  - "In Commemoration of the 200th Anniversary of the Birth of Immanuel Kant" undated (Box 824.2, Folder 11)
  - "Influence on the College of the Demands and Expectations of its Graduates" undated (Box 824.2, Folder 12)
  - "Milton", First Church of Northampton 1908 (Box 824.2, Folder 13)
  - Phi Beta Kappa Initiation 1923 (Box 824.2, Folder 14)
  - "Philosophers and Philoderers" 1920 (Box 824.2, Folder 15)
  - "Philosophy and Religion" 1927 (Box 824.2, Folder 16)
  - "The Resurrection of Jesus and its Bearing on the Problem of Human Immortality" 1901 (Box 824.2, Folder 17)
  - "Robert Elsmere" undated (Box 824.2, Folder 18)
  - "The Social Functions of Philosophy", Yale Philosophy Club 1924 (Box 824.2, Folder 19)
  - "Unity of the Sciences in Logic", Smith College Graduates Club 1917 (Box 824.2, Folder 20)
- SERIES VIII. WRITINGS, MISC.
  - "The Connection of the Body and the Soul" undated (Box 824.3, Folder 1)
  - "Pragmatism" for Discussion at the Club 1905 (Box 824.3, Folder 2)
  - "the Rise of the Modern Doctrine of Evolution: A Sketch" undated (Box 824.3, Folder 3)
  - "Teleology in the Modern Philosophy of Nature" undated (Box 824.3, Folder 4)
  - Other Items: Jonathan Edwards: A Retrospect ed. By H.N. Gardiner. Boston and New York: Houghton, Mifflin and Co. 1901 (WS) 1901 (Box shelf)